http://www.pumptronics.ca/company/privacy-policy

REQUEST A QUOTECLIENT LOGINCONTACT US1-888-222-6676
HomeWhy PumptronicsSolutionsAgricultureOil and GasESP Transfer StationsBoosterCommercialSewage Lift SystemsWater Feature PumpsIndustrialMunicipalHousing Development Irrigation SystemsHigh Rise Booster StationsLeed and Rain Water SystemsGolf & TurfSports FieldsGolf CoursesCustomCustomer ServicePumps
TypesApplicationsFInancingRequest a quoteClient LoginSuccess StoriesResources
DownloadsFAQ'sLinksGalleryGlossaryCompany
About UsTeamPartnersCareersContact UsRequest A QuotePrivacy PolicyTerms Of Use
Privacy Policy
Protecting Your Privacy
Protecting your privacy is important to Pumptronics Pumping Systems ("PUMPTRONICS"). This Privacy Policy explains how PUMPTRONICS collects, uses, and discloses the personal information you may provide while using the PUMPTRONICS Web site at www.Pumptronics.ca, and the content, information and services provided through the Web site (collectively the "Web Site").
YOUR CONSENT
1. Consent - By using the Web Site, you signify your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, you may not use the Web Site.
INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED
2. Information - Like many other Web sites, the Web Site automatically collects certain information regarding Web Site users, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, the IP address of your Internet Service Provider, the date and time you access the Web Site, the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to the Web Site, the operating system you are using, the sections of the Web Site you visit, the Web Site pages accessed and information viewed. This information is used only for Web Site and system administration purposes and to improve the Web Site.
3. Cookies - The Web Site may use "cookies", a technology that installs information on a Web Site user's computer to permit the Web Site to recognize future visits using that computer. Cookies enhance the convenience and use of the Web Site. For example, the information provided through cookies is used to recognize you as a previous user of the Web Site, to track your activity at the Web Site in order to respond to your needs, to offer personalized Web page content and information for your use, to automatically populate online forms with your personal information for your convenience, and to otherwise facilitate your Web Site experience. You may choose to decline cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may affect your use of the Web Site and your ability to access or use certain Web Site features.
PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU SPECIFICALLY PROVIDE
4. Your Personal Information - During your use of certain web pages on the Web Site, you may be asked to voluntarily provide personal information (such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone number) and information regarding your interest in PUMPTRONICS.
5. Use of Your Personal Information - PUMPTRONICS may use your personal information to contact and correspond with you, to respond to your communications, to facilitate and enhance your use of the Web Site, to provide you with information and services requested through the Web Site, and as otherwise permitted by law. PUMPTRONICS may develop a confidential user profile for you, which will be used to facilitate your use of the Web Site. Additionally, PUMPTRONICS may keep a record of all communications with you.
6. E-mails - PUMPTRONICS may send to you, from time to time, e-mail or other communications containing information about PUMPTRONICS and other matters it believes will interest you. At any time you may ask PUMPTRONICS to stop sending you e-mail and other information by contacting This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. PUMPTRONICS may use non-personal information to create aggregate tracking information reports regarding Web Site user demographics and the use of the Web Site, and then provide those reports to others. PUMPTRONICS also may link tracking information with Web Site users' personal information. Once such a link is made, all of the linked information is treated as personal information and will be used and disclosed only in accordance with this Policy.
7. Disclosure of Your Personal Information - PUMPTRONICS may disclose your personal information in the following circumstances:
a. Disclosure to Authorizing Persons - If your access to the Web Site has been authorized by a PUMPTRONICS customer, PUMPTRONICS may provide your personal information to that authorizing person. PUMPTRONICS has no control over authorizing persons' use of your personal information, and that use is not necessarily subject to this Policy. If you do not wish your personal information to be disclosed to the person who has authorized your use of the Web Site, you may not use the Web Site.
b. Disclosure in Business Transfers - In the event that PUMPTRONICS is involved in the sale or transfer of some or all of its business, as part of that sale or transfer, PUMPTRONICS may disclose your personal information to the acquiring organization, but will require the acquiring organization to agree to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If at any time you do not wish PUMPTRONICS to disclose your personal information as part of the sale or transfer of some or all of its business, please notify PUMPTRONICS at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
c. Law Enforcement and Legal Disclosure - PUMPTRONICS may disclose your personal information to a government institution that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information or where PUMPTRONICS has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful in the investigation of unlawful activity, or to comply with a subpoena or warrant or an order made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction to compel the production of information, or to comply with court rules regarding the production of records and information, or to their legal counsel.
d. Location of Information - PUMPTRONICS will process and store your personal information in Oakville, ON, Canada.
e. Securing Your Information - To help protect the confidentiality of your personal information, PUMPTRONICS employs security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. Nevertheless, due to the nature of Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and PUMPTRONICS cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy.
f. Accessing Your Personal Information - You may request access to your personal information and information about PUMPTRONICS collection, use and disclosure of that information by contacting PUMPTRONICS at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information, and will be entitled to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and to have it amended as appropriate. You can help PUMPTRONICS maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying PUMPTRONICS of any changes to your personal information.
OTHER MATTERS
11. Other Web Sites - The Web Site may contain links to other Web sites or Internet resources. When you click on one of those links you are contacting another Web site or Internet resource that may collect information about you voluntarily or through cookies or other technologies. PUMPTRONICS has no responsibility or liability for or control over those other Web sites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. You should review the privacy policies of those other Web sites and Internet resources to understand how they collect and use information.
12. Privacy Policy Changes - To accommodate changes in the Web Site, changing technology, and legal developments, this Policy may be changed from time to time in PUMPTRONICS' sole discretion and without any prior notice or liability to you or any other person. The collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by PUMPTRONICS will be governed by the version of this Policy in effect at that time. New versions of this Policy will be posted here. Your continued use of the Web Site subsequent to any changes to this Policy will signify that you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the changed Policy. Accordingly, when you use the Web Site you should check the date of this Policy and review any changes since the last version. You should also bookmark this page and periodically review this Policy to ensure that you are familiar with the most current version.
13. Your Comments - If you have any comments or questions about this Policy or your personal information, please contact PUMPTRONICS at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
About UsTeamPartnersCareersContact UsRequest A QuotePrivacy PolicyTerms Of Use
Login
Remember Me
Log in
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Create an account
Request A Quote
Read More
Financing Available
Read More
Industrial Water Pumping Systems
Industrial environments are particularly demanding for pumping systems. You could be pumping fluids that are under high pressure ...
Learn more
Golf Course Pump Stations
Large amounts of water are required to maintain the quality of turf demanded by athletes and golfers. Depending on the location ...
Learn more
Custom Water Management Solutions
Pumptronics was founded on the premise of designing, building, installing and servicing custom, automated pumping solutions ...
Learn more
Oil and Gas Industry Water Pumps
The Oil and Gas industry faces a number of challenges in recovering fossil fuels. The methods that are chosen are dependent on ...
Learn more
HomeWhy PumptronicsSolutionsAgricultureOil and GasESP Transfer StationsBoosterCommercialSewage Lift SystemsWater Feature PumpsIndustrialMunicipalHousing Development Irrigation SystemsHigh Rise Booster StationsLeed and Rain Water SystemsGolf & TurfSports FieldsGolf CoursesCustomCustomer ServicePumps
TypesApplicationsFInancingRequest a quoteClient LoginSuccess StoriesResources
DownloadsFAQ'sLinksGalleryGlossaryCompany
About UsTeamPartnersCareersContact UsRequest A QuotePrivacy PolicyTerms Of Use
Offcanvas
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua.
